#### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### Giancarlo Boas Rueda

gianbo251@gmail.com

Contact Number: (+49) 172 2970788 Birthdate: 8th August 1990 – Lima, Peru

Bachelor Degree in Communications with a degree in Marketing and Advertisement. Interested in the areas of Customer Experience, social communications, and financial education. Experience in events organization, Customer experience, training of personnel, conflict-solution, brand and social communication.

#### **Work Experience**

Supplementary staff as a caring assistant KM Catholic Association for Social Services in Osnabrück e.V (Since April 2023)

- · Carer in one housing group for migrant young people
- Accompany the migrant young people to different appointments
- · Assist the migrant young people on different tasks

## Customer Support Representative for Playstation SYKES EMEA (January 2022- October 2022)

- Assist customers with Software issues with the PlayStation Network via Email, Telephone and Online Chat
- Process Refunds for purchases made in the PlayStation Network
- Process Customers information about the issues to build a Databank of the most common issues

# Freelance Spanish teacher (February 2020 – January 2022)

 Teaching Spanish to students from different parts of the world creating personalized methods for each student depending on their interests

## Teacher assistant (Volunteer) – Schulenheit Primarschule Eichbüel (May 2019 – July 2019)

- Assist the head teacher of the classroom to teach German to foreign students in Switzerland
- Responsible of accomplish the schedule of classwork to the students in the classroom
- Responsible of organize small activities in the classroom with learning objectives

# Project Manager & General Coordinator - Kiya Peru Positive Action (September 2017 – March 2019)

- Provide leadership, strategic direction, coordination, and evaluation of all aspects of all Kiya projects in Peru
- Oversee staff involved with all projects, work with the onsite staff of the projects both in Peru and in the UK to
  ensure the projects continue to progress to improve outcomes for all children and families
- · Manage finances of all projects, ensuring that all funds are allocated/spent correctly
- Assume the role of Legal Representative of the NGO in Peru
- · Local fundraising and networking

## Project Manager & Volunteers Coordinator - Kiya Peru Positive Action (November 2016 – September 2017)

- Provided leadership, strategic direction, coordination, and evaluation of all aspects of the charity-run children's home
- Oversaw staff involved with the Outreach therapy program, related to the children's home
- Managed all aspects of the Individual Volunteer Program, ensuring a seamless transition from enquiry and booking to training and support
- Ensured that all participants have an outstanding experience of volunteering with Kiya Survivors

### Customer Experience Protection Specialist - Banco de Crédito BCP (June 2013 – November 2015)

- Responsible for reviewing that the communications of the bank are written in a language handle by all the customers and that they were aligned with the bank regulations
- Responsible to assist telemarketing area in customer experience following the Bank self-regulations.
- Consultant for the units of products and distribution channel in retail banking for transparency of information and bank self-regulation topics
- Administrator of the virtual education platform of all the agencies for training and teaching about the transparency
  of information
- Member of the staff in the online program of Financial Education that the bank broadcast for the customers

## Quality service Intern - Banco de Crédito BCP (October 2012 – June 2013)

- Responsible of organizing all the events of the area
- Responsible of support the units of products and distribution channels in retail banking about quality of service and customer experience
- Responsible to organizing the training of the personnel of the bank to improve the customer service attention
- Support in the repositioning of the brand with the bank personnel

#### **Educational Certifications**

- Bachelor's degree in "Communications" faculty of the "Universidad de Lima"
- Specialization Degree in "Marketing & advertising" faculty of Communication of the "Universidad de Lima"
- Advance English Course completed at "Asociación Cultural Peruano Británica (Británico)
- Certification for teaching Spanish as a foreign language at "Colegio de Español Tia Tula"

### Informatic Knowdlege

- Microsoft office
- Adobe Design tools Basic
- MacOS edition program Basic
- Photography knowledge

#### Language Knowdlege

- Spanish Native
- English advanced (fluent)
- German Intermediate (B2 level)